Let me be wrong once
right and I will head.
About. Yesterday to fundraise you
get Nasri still out when you
find Mr Tracy would you ask him if he
would come to send one to take it to the
reportorial shop and they deserve to know
you don't mind Oh no sir I don't mind
spending there like
a number sit around him up yes. Well that
here Mr Bostwick always say the students
want to be doing you Mr Boss
but don't you remember it was
a promotional tie up to increase circulation
and what did I promise them. They
would work for you for three days as we
report and the one who supports the best
story during that time was to receive
fifty dollars and the Goldman might have
guessed I don't know why I let you
talk me into these things last week at
a place filled with
a lot of champion potato pickets and now
the place is going to be on account of
about
a crazy Cup I will just speak
I decided to. Oh Mr Bostic
these are the young people you've been so
anxious to make this message through from
the bin but scoop
a young lady from bank I.
Miss him who love. Are
really going to have real assignments just
like real reporting right or wrong or
exactly what might happen why not cover
it cannot go boy Mr Boss be able to say
a few words to the contestants. Or anyone
is simple minded enough to want to work
on
a newspaper I've never been able to find
out for this to past week journalism is
a very noble and glorious career with all
the adventure and romance and everything
I should think you just not that I do love
it I love every minute of. My employees
to. Take one. Look.
At UVA and got to write a story about
a squirrel in the car with me and.
I got to find out how many B.B.Q.
Sauce with a human interest story about
a goldfish maybe sanitary
poetry good thing a T.V.
Room one all right now c'mon get going all
right children come on come on and it
isn't no you needn't bother coming back
clever idea isn't going to go into that
later if the past week I don't believe you
take it seriously my dear Miss who is in
regard to your supposition I see
you're not without first because.
I still haven't been able to find
Mr Tracy every time I get on
a reformed upper crust Oh right leave in
the mornings does well I'm not really on
the court I was right away there holding
an inquest on that Lambert woman yes or
yes in the service.
I you satisfied with your assignment this
group Oh I think you do so I salute you.
Dr Kerry please. Raise your right hand
whether it was money or
a lot of good will be the truth the whole
truth nothing about it and how can I do
your declaring Here's our country
surgeon you examined the body
a kid member I did it when I did you find
that Mrs Lander's death was not caused by
heart failure as Africa but
started her death was caused by
a poisoned sodium Fahrenheit
what is sodium for an eye it's
a chemical used in photography it's such
a chemical easily obtained on not only
on special order manufacture It's
a new agent not yet on the open market in
fact only those who are well advanced in
photography know anything about. Miles
limber the language or the person back to
Act does not matter that's all there I
was. What aroused the others patients
well for years Dr Hibberd had
a sure that my aunt's heart condition was
nothing to worry. And when she died so
suddenly I was naturally very shocked and
surprised but even so I didn't suspect
anything until I happened to run across
a scientific magazine in my aunt's library
that was an article in that magazine
which had
a great deal of significance to me in the
older circumstances the article was about
sodium Fahrenheit and the portions of
the dealing with the chemical poisonous
properties had been carefully marked
and. The goal of this magazine Velo
it's addressed to you madame in your market
article Miss Denning why. I must add
why. I keep
a file of all can because I work with the
poisonous ones in there and then you are
interested in the dug. Out
a million I was sold in fat and when I I
know something about it is downing What
was your relationship to Kate lamb my mother
was her companion for many years after
Mother died Mrs Lander to me isn't it true
that under the terms of Mr Lambert will
you were the sole beneficiary
Yes. But I didn't kill him when I
can't remember was the best friend I ever
had she put me through school treated me
as her own child and yet
you caused her into making
a will leaving all her property to you
know a will that was made less than
a week before her there no I didn't do it
so I must have taken the poison but the
doc room Mr Garrett if you had the chemical
to that would prove I was innocent Oh
well well the matter is fingerprints would
be on it now I think being removed but
they couldn't be rebuilt if anyone touch
that chemical the found I would edge the
prints into the metal Such has been made
that poison get damaged and it's messy but
it must be in the house somewhere it's
done and you are the only person connected
with an amber House or the knowledge of
sodium found You're the only one who had
access to Ms man was real the night she
died and you were the only one who I voted
to commit I didn't feel like it why didn't
I think can I play one that's all. She.
Wants about it the demi
girls been over Dr Martin.
What's up they think so they're going
to figure out I got better John about
a don't care.
Oh wait.
What's all this about attempts to explain
the principle to the cops when we first
got to be the jack jam.
Never mind how good
a dummy of the south look at all Italy's
don't seek and it's insane that the money
goes to my mom not bad. How much do you
get the number to take care of me.
So I don't stop being nice to the
bandit guys nobody but me lamb. By.
The Chemical Safety. It may have been
the
a profit of the straw man I want to get in
here with out or are I'm here to see that
oh well i made them to my bedroom right
away and all I had glamour and. You have to
. See if I could of gone in that
case miss you I'll just take
a look around well maybe you may go on the
side of the house before the war when we
have just a good idea and
a response I'm getting
I'll come around that. Way
when you don't know. Why.
I'm here in the guest. I've
been there all runnin hitter Hey man I'm
up for charges if you pay to have it fixed
Wow. Blue Square let me
copy three and I've had my
kind of makes me about fifty cents for the
gasoline I wanted coming out here so.
Here's
a dollar back all right
you know you. Can see. On
our money for
a gas meter it or maybe I'm in the wrong
branch of the service. He was from the gas
company. That's kind of funny. I got
to talk to you on the popularity
I was into the light on
a common man and even my fender and
I shot of. You switch that was
a sign misled that. I thought reporters
always did things like that they do in the
movies and besides That's right
my textbook on journalism in
a newspaper man I'm going to stop at nothing
to get news and if you ever intend to
press the editor she would be willing to
do much more than just what the salmon
calls for so they're going like this what
happened with me I have been everywhere
it been functional I bet you twenty three
you never thought I could do it just
drove the story of the man but
inquest was on the street
a half hour ago. But that's
impossible I had it right.
We were lucky enough to get
it from the D.A.'s office.
Here I was so sure I had
a scoop you'd have to stop the presses stop
the presses some my dear little girlie
Will you please take pity on
a poor tired old man if another thing like
this happens to me today I lose my mind
.
The writing down good morning. Well the
star reporter this morning don't mention
you watch I'll show that Mr Boss
Did you ever his name is I'll get
a story yeah abscess per minute and
think. Oh I'm good and you're not
this why am I likely to be you oh shucks
Miss Nancy that's just plain ole serial.
Said I have a favor I want to ask
of you go right ahead I am in
a very receptive mood this morning go right
ahead well you would then need the good
lawyer and I want you to defend her and
I would want that case Nancy I've been
reading about it and I'm afraid the girl
is guilty of not one bit of extenuating
evidence just the same of it she didn't
do it makes you think that I don't know I
guess maybe it's just my woman's intuition
but she doesn't look at the type of boys
and anybody I go by type matching on the
most charming woman in history with
a murderous and she committed her crime
for far less glamorous space that's where
the man with
a twenty year came in on to you what are
you talking about this man sat next to me
during inquest and
afterwards got my car with
a woman and ran into my friend there and
you're going to take that car when you can
start having accidents and it wasn't my
fault I wasn't even in the car wow did I
mean to pay for that vendor to what did
he went right after that my mistake in
trying to get in probably another reporter
I don't think so he didn't look smart
enough to have to drop the suspicion if I
would concern myself about it too much or
one of the many I'm saving it for
the rest all. What about it.
The the.
The it's. In the
garage. Why do you want.
This.
Well I read. What's
about what I am writing
for the drama stop it well
yes nothing excited over.
It over. The thing I step back I
might in the privacy of my family.
Just aren't. I What's
Obama. Back to me it's just
a practical joke sure it blows up on your
precious daughter and boy did you go into
what tailspin technician I'll bet you put
that thing in the I don't be an infant.
I've got better things to do. I think
it's time to be in the middle then should
anyone would never do
a trick I had or I. I
think. I was you know. I got
a lot out there not mine you know
killer per kid you grow up to be
a freak but I was Mary's idea it certainly
was very interesting you want to be
ashamed. That you want to speak to your
sister that gangster she's out of my
control or you're just jealous because you
didn't think but first you have no way
the running of I think well they don't know
how I want to get out of here before I
do is control myself. I'm not
black I don't you dare commit
a. Crime my friend not want
my pants it's like wow.
That was. Nice going there and
see the very young I did just
a nice quiet morning of the Druids Well
obviously you know when you go on what do
you think I'll be going this tennis racket
to shovel call I'll tell you where you
go in for ten cents I wouldn't pay one
penny I'm not that interested in what am I
going for you get my
house. Anyway he's got
a date with you girl you're going
to play tennis again with that that
woman what do you mean woman she's only
two years older than you are well rather
play tennis all right but I was started
to pending on you to help me because my
getting the best story for the paper isn't
really so important but you know how it
is the honor and everything would be nice
gosh now if you know all right go ahead
to my me I just. Have to when I have
something for you or you know what is it
really just
a little birthday present. I spent the
four bucks ahead if it's the fender well.
Jean Nancy thanks. But my birthday
isn't for two months that's so. Oh
well now that you've seen it you might
as well keep it. What. Do you think so I
think I don't want. All.
She. Thinks you're welcome
wait
a minute Nancy look I'm I postpone my
telestrator if you really need Oh don't bother
don't bother I was just going out to Janet
if you know Denning and I want you to
take your camera along so far
she has not anyone to take
a picture on how to expect me to
get one zero zero zero I think of
a way. Then you don't really need me
where all the corners always take their
photographers when they're when they're
on important assignments and besides Dan
doesn't like the idea of my going to jail
alone I'll go yet again there's no place
for children Mary Nichols then I'll let
her go maybe the lack of rock should say
not my going to change your clothes and
where you have all right I bet you can't
wait to have. Her I will make
a new addition and besides maybe you'll
have time to fix my friend. Do you think
and. No cameras Well you see
I have
a lady you can read ten zero zero
OK all right over there. Let's
That shouldn't you couldn't get
a camera in this place. Was
in the case I took out the camera put in
a block of wood I think it had something
like this look you don't expect me to take
a picture in here after what you said. And
if they catch us we'll stay here or stop
you work. In Sun You never saw
a real newspaper man that's how.
You need him. Now and I'm not like
that looks awful. For gosh sakes
what do you join he just gave
a time you don't know how many.
Exodus right. Or you're that.
Way Now you look like a real reporter not
a store window dummy. Here's
the standard I'm going to Drew of the
Tribune and this is just makes my
photographer. Seem so you know I guess
I better explain we're not real
reporters I just want to win
a prize in journalism and that's why I
wanted need of you what'd you say your name
was Drew are you related to Carson
grow the attorney is your father Oh I
see you standing do you know a man with
a funny ear it's all sort of ordered up
like I go around us but there was one of
the inquest and I was wondering if he was
a friend of yours I don't know who we could
be standing I don't think you did and.
That is I mean I think you're innocent.
It's all right with you I'm going to ask my
father to come and see you oh if you
only would you see the well the so much
evidence against me. It's even worse now
than it was yesterday they find something
else police checked with the manufacturers
and learned the only sale of sodium
there and I've made in this part of the
country was to me. Which. If you only had
their team can the one the poison came in
you know you talk about the in question
yesterday disappeared someone probably
started I thought just beyond the day when I
was cleaning out the door I can understand
why they didn't find it what butts and.
Tim was empty I didn't throw it away. Why
just say that because the manufacturers
of this was honest think hard I think I
remember what you did what I put some empty
bottles and things in the basement and all
covered by container must have been with
them maybe it's still
a hair yeah you just leave it to me please
don't tell anyone I almost forgot you
standing there would take
a picture of you. And her you
have to. Stay. And we'll
let you know what happens.
A little bit to right now hold it.
Here that's the big idea that's going
on out here one take McConnell from the
border with one fell down and spray I'm
sorry is gentle with the president and I
think we're going to be leaving.
But what if you can't get it it's still
illegal not to report him Where is the
right to do things an ordinary person
should. Go ahead and do just exactly as I
told you OK but if anything
happens don't blame me.
Oh wow. You don't want to subscribe in
a magazine story oh I didn't think you
did. Are you watching us when I say
yeah. Well I guess you get kind
of wholesome around here all by
yourself sometimes. I'm a very busy
right now if you like I could play
a little gamma rummy or something.
Say ass and I hear sound drop
a chance Wow. Look at you mind if I
sit over there I'm kind of
superstitious Oh sure sure.
We are to have something to shoot
that shot so they and they appoint
a penny Oh. Yeah that'll be
fine. I'll keep score for it.
Harder hour the really saying they're.
Very good my oh they don't deliver
that puts me off my game.
It's all right.
That night. Was not. Arrested it
was just you were just you're.
Going to actually get to ride the
next. Well I'm going to have to
because. We started figure that.
You got me in
a fight. I lost my whole which allows for
that Rummy shark but it was worth it I
found it in Cambodia. And to put me with
a funny you chased me out of the
basement. We took an awful chance.
Maybe we should not gonna we're going to
get this team right down to the police
station and seed capital in
finding fingerprints on.
Suffering cats
a lot of the time my time as they was at
three did much more important than taking
my pastor out this time shall never play
with me again I don't want to get the
Playstation You don't need me you
can tell me about it later go by.
People it be you.
Well understand I want to get away.
Yes well that you know that you know. What
are you doing up so late going back to
sleep when I. Go to sleep.
Now come on and tell me all about.
Now said you've always taught me to do
right haven't you tried to not think.
If I believed something I knew which right
I should know and developed with and I
don't back down to make. You make
a promise to do which right. He said My
original failed to live up to his promise
the way you'd never want me to break
a promise would you course. You make
a promise in good faith I'd expect you to
live up to it when I want to cost you and
you help me live up to it suddenly kind of
a part of you think I am well then you're
going to depend you're getting because I
promised her you would was not dead
you just said you'd help me keep
a promise man so you tricked me into this
you're always doing that to me and I'm
going to have well all right if you can
give me any reason to believe that your
dining is innocent I'll take your
case. Why do you work with her
did not have that man as best you know and
I think didn't sound that can of soda in
fact you want to be standing kind could
have had bigger prints on you two when I
was there alone and I know it was important
evidence because that never the front
of your case you have
a basement. That's not the worst of it
when I was ignited out of the trees
a woman stolen from me so that probably
the other people are mixed up and you
should have gone to the police in the first
place I know everything's gone I failed
all around here I'm just not intelligent
that's what I said I mean darling
everybody makes mistakes.
I don't just think
that it's going to be gospel which is
not the only of maybe things that I'm
responsible for but no more and then say
I'll see you as any person or I would
guess how does that feel ten years younger
Don't be so one of the ethics so father
is in the thick of evidence were taken to
court so we'll see if you can get hold of
that name of the fund he did I think is
not going to go so I'm that yes I'll say
look I thought that the fossil programs
have the power now but I'm going to
confound them I thought you said like I
said understand you Nancy but how can you
expect to be specially around I've got to
say that profit that's no way to talk to
your father object all why don't you take
them out of town do you know start all
over again how does that man look like
one of these purple great I said it was
probably a cauliflower ear that
might indicate that he was
a boxer already. What connection such
a man could have with this case and more
than I can say that I so long as that man
with the funny it was
a clue I think you want to do something
about it and I'm going to do something
about a girl with
a funny face and I'm baby you're going
to bed. I don't think you'll always be
a daddy's baby the body baby and everybody
would be enough for the baby that's why
I'm in love with you
pretty bad. Break the bank
a. Couple. Good night they be good
night baby good night baby I'm going
to leave you now. Gotta talk to
her in the morning the morning bright
and early morning now we are going to.
If you shine I'm sure I drop
a chance. Thank you I think.
You keep pictures of the
prize fighters people like that you should
meet some of my wife's folks but you
came to the right places there and I'm
normal personally but you're going to look
like oh you know I mean the minute
you have that kind of power here.
Here. It recognizing let me know.
What I want. I'm going to.
How did you find me. I got
a way with unexpected find to be. Not
a good guy and he's not so pretty I think
so what's on your mind with this good
thing I found when he. Actually
ends Susan in Nassau Camembert
used to be
a boxer and right now he's at Maxis you
made him for STREET HOW DO YOU KNOW HOW DO
YOU KNOW. I just asked
myself where I go if I were
a prize fighter and decided to do
a gymnasium so I called the place in
town and pretended I was just rants and
girlfriend pretty soon I found out and I
hung up. Well it was nice of you to tell
me about it I gotta get back. To me I don't
want to keep you I just want to let you
know where I'll be and take that I ask you
you're not going down to the gym alone
question him something has to be done about
talk to you right away never did so you
came over here to tell me about
a song of the jam with your father by
letting your go of it I did no such thing
you're not responsible for me well we
didn't smoke but still we still are I hope.
You too will not go why not never mind Don
And that's you know you got me worried
maybe I better go I don't
think you wanted to it's
a pretty tough place I can take care of
myself and you too. You want to hear what
some of your costs to your post another
box about the name of one mom to gain
talking confidence and who knows maybe I'm
going to say you had this offer your god
didn't I didn't exist and I did not.
Invent.
This is an awesome challenge.
Where she lives and you'd
like to know she's got
a new brain to work. To remember. I'm.
Still alive it's true you can
always get information from with.
Or without. QUESTION It doesn't
look very friendly doesn't.
Want.
No chance. You're trying like. I'm
kind of new or. I've been put on
a campus. That they did not see
what an eye for the name and
what's your name. Even
though never heard of it. I
very well known around here. On
if you know. I'm going to do it
trying to say your five year
entry although. I didn't.
Teach them A.J.
. Drum goes from how to do
things that interest you.
But I'd really rather not.
Actually you know this is such. When you
haven't told me that as soon as you can.
Right here.
Oh. No no.
No. But I'm going to. Make it your.
I want to. No. I can't I got
a. I got mobbed or something if I
don't. Look maybe. Yeah like an office.
Let's go right. Well.
Nancy. Now folks are going to have
a little excited. Boxing
exhibition for exactly after
a good combo we all know I am.
So glad. I am one of the commodified.
You. Are
a genius. I can only.
Be good at it I am.
Sure you don't know what's going to get.
How much time left. Till I
am.
I am.
A.
You. Try.
And. Make
a friend that. Is
. Not just has to be. Sure.
I want to. Know. With
a tennis teacher. His teacher.
I mean I've seen about you
less. Nothing nothing.
Oh. Give me
a cookie. To. Find out. OK.
This is Mr. I. Got from.
The place. Yeah yeah.
You know what I missed.
I'll see if you got the message. Is
there to. Know there's no message was
grabbed his. Just
a moment or drawl. She
went to the Mandarin crappy Mr
Ranson thank you but I give.
You
a money. Right. Why don't you. Why
. Don't we kill or.
To get. A hold.
Of my dead body. Will. Have to come.
But on one condition the waiter take
your order say I'm not hungry. Or we
have
a lot of money are you going to cooperate
or not particular to our place to go what
I'm going to. Try not on the what. Have
no. We can't buy you any.
Case. Why do you. Ask more.
This is.
The hill she had to be. Putting
right out of Everson to find out
labyrinth moving in
a level that he told. His review was drawn
and what the third he joins with the
motor or her driver break we're
going to are surprised I took up
a tin can with find
a prince on it. I don't
want to do it by. The
next I want to bring another
that. Was over with
a lot of it with. Some of the boys. To
the surface.
I don't. I don't know I
think. What has to the.
Laboratory was rather mild
Lamb I was. Wondering I said.
I'm not sure you. Have.
If I. Was to that's how we
got. Medio trust as always
you're sure you nice people I charge you
a hotel thank you very
much money we've got her
a sixty five. Which you just did you tell
me Mr we got to go home and get the money
from our folks who will come back sixty
five. Now look what you've got us
into we don't know
nothin about do we kill.
Mr we haven't. Got no sixty five.
When that got. Us
a little boy the defense bill
Keegan with the idea. I'm certain.
You'll watch you do you
see. This in that way I
was about with. The ice. I was trying to
provide for you're going to wash dishes
also do you realize. Maybe he didn't.
Yeah he's
a machine. You tried to do.
I'm sure he said all of the.
All night you should Nijmegen
sounds good why should.
They. Always. Be in fly back
to. Mr Can't you read. The.
Small. But he knows.
All. The bank the all.
Song on one side. Of
the baseball. When
the. Head of.
The in
a I want to copy the the. Omega the.
Dog.
In the world. The. Ha
the it was.
All blah blah blah blah was so hard why
go Diebold memos an article I want
the song for
the it was. That was
the
song go Bob. It's the way.
The quote. Was when. The
upgrade with the rom the age of the. The
bomb.
The in.
Come. The
the in.
The the. Calmest
we have all but. Here was a fifty
dollars and the best and now it's just
a bust because shows the best news story
submitted by out shopping for the price
was about the humane work a
wind vendor did not crack up
a two foot square with. Me. It is
a great investment still has
a better story told me to buy
he said I come to the shops.
Well what is it. Is Mr Brodrick
some strange man called.
He had to be seen to have sodium. Fingerprints
on it that would prove you were dead
. To the religious people have.
Bothered to take. I would tell him. One.
Thing the tens of thousands of seeds to
repeat. It's trying to stop the rest of you
want to commit troops home page one to
replace the story yet every rock. Spinning
like
a half would give you the money he once
regulate the dominate the and I take great
pleasure in presenting you the check. And
so many. Give the checks because it's not
how you take the metal
content for analyzing.
The the little
the the little.
More. Remarkable there was still
something after the spill the beans
a. Distinct such an interest in that
story isn't true must be true for the
paper Nancy just made up of the printed
part of Drew at the top of the newspapers
the days when you therefore I made the
others think the story was on the level why
. There was no interest are you sure Captain
who you will be back sure I'm sure she
called on
a radio interview on how to avoid crime
he's done it all right just the same I'll
bet he'd understand was cut and when he
got that I haven't got well so I want to
thank. You look Sergeant I put that story
in the paper so the police could track
the real murderer of Kate Lambert's world
that's different home to to see that
paper be on the street any minute this
method is really murder you go to sexism
after that in tandem if you resist or if
you think Fox is going to double cross the
recency must rule for convulsive and you've
got something cos I had to all you had
to do is be
a saucy face and I'm going to rot in prison
both with the evidence for this guy's
doctor that will make this seem dull and
our hotel we're going to have not yet if I
want to give him time but I've got to go
home I want to get my was used to about
how you handle the case when you read what
I write you probably because the did you
see what you made all right you
kids got a pulse but you got
a problem oh sure it was once.
Was a start and puts on
a couple spots in the East you might want
to have those Nancy police around they'll
run away on this get rid of that Vance
is that what you mean all right all the
world catch on the thing was meant to be
much better but to save an see you or to
worry about that they'll never know me
aware that this guy the war McCulloch case
you're uncertain. For.
The first. Something.
That I'm. Old sure Rummel.
The last time she
was here with. My mother
is the used to be.
Well it's the thing is occupied with it is
proper that I can give you the one right
next to the day has to happen as the icy.
Property of seventeen. Stores bigger.
Yes.
And the moment. Thank you.
The prospect. Of your sergeant or.
Anything happens. Right.
He did that with.
The club wants.
The of
I don't like this this.
Is it when one has to.
Also. Know you're going to be.
The
in.
The. Old.
Love the five. Hundred the Bible.
What's your name. Little over
the in.
The
fold the shot I'm going to.
The reason. I got out of.
The There was. I didn't
hear.
What they did so I just
mentioned. I don't.
Know. That you have. To
get. The idea. Of
the bomb.
Our are. Here all the time you want
to do something. I can't remember.
This but I'm all lies.
I was not asked for that so that's not
I chose the cross to be some way off.
That was just
a fuse box. Say. Doesn't but use it
to the electric sun if we turned up
we get some attention they would
notice a Polish baby by that time
a bit too much this. Way
because. I've got the idea.
That the creative station
and this whole house.
The
size. Of
the city.
In.
The
US. The
Gotta catch. The in.
The process. He calls it. Dinner
that's.
The price. To watch
a story in the paper. But is still hanging
out of it and can I feel him on his I
have to prove who killed him I don't trust
just tell it like but that's never going
to double cross you don't think I have
a lawyer you. Already jump from looking
for that and can't save yourself right.
The
of the way. The on
the on
the on the on
the on my surprises.
The only.
Way my daughter caught
the
eight
the.
The
. The
all the.
Cars. All
the all the the crowd. That feel
that's the point the Lambert and here's the
Bulls the as the how many times when I
told you not so good how dare you allow
my daughter. The ha ha ha ha the
AHA HA HA HA HA HA HA
HA to what it was all
a car was made to chat with it
at perhaps an kid or a girl
a pain to buy extra.
Away.